I'm going to see I'm going to watch os loock's video it's
voy a ver voy a ver el vídeo de os loock
already 3:15 man I can't be there much longer
es que ya son las 3:15 tío mucho más no
because I have to record a
puedo estar porque tengo que grabar un
couple of videos also for telesalseo
par de vídeos también para telesalseo
let's see the success and fall of orsl
vamos a ver el éxito y la caída de orsl
Back let's see
Back vamos a ver
the let's see the success and fall of
el vamos a ver el éxito y la caída de
orlock I've never been able to say
orlock nunca he sabido decir
orlock
orlock
orlock the success of the fall of
orlock el éxito de la caída de
orlock but I don't know what fall I mean the
orlock pero no sé cuál caída O sea la
fall literally is that T for whatever reason
caída literalmente es que el T pues por
has stopped making content
lo que sea ha dejado de hacer contenido
or rather because things were never going badly for him I mean
o sea porque mal nunca le iba o sea
orlock is one of the few creators who
orlock es de los pocos creadores que de
could suddenly go
repente podían [__]
and upload a video a month and the video had
y subir un vídeo al mes y el vídeo tenía
200 300 400,000 views I don't understand
200 300 400,000 visitas no lo entiendo
honestly when normally YouTube
la verdad cuando normalmente YouTube te
punishes you eh if you don't upload content and you
castiga eh si tú no subes contenido y no
're not active it punishes you although the
estás activo te castiga si bien la
career of a content creator
carrera de un creador de contenido
public figure is not free from
figura pública no se Libra de las
controversy Not necessarily all of these
polémicas No necesariamente todas estas
stories are doomed to end badly
historias están condenadas a acabar mal
and This is one of those
y Esta es una de esas
stories fallen by the same clear fall
historias caída por el mismo claro caída
[ __ ] Wake up wake up wake up not
[__] Despierta Despierta Despierta no
only well he  he stopped making videos for
solo bueno él dejó de hacer vídeos para
the main channel which man became
el canal principal que tío llegó durante
my favorite youtuber for a while eh
un tiempo a ser mi youtuber favorito eh
I loved his videos but he left
Me encantaban sus vídeos pero dejó dejó
the main channel to
el canal principal para para hacer
stream only stream and uploaded others on a
Stream solo Stream y subí tros en en un
secondary channel which I think the
canal secundario que creo que el canal
secondary channel had more
secundario llegó a tener más
subscribers than the main one play
suscriptores que el principal jugar al
LoL stop playing LoL your life is
LoL deja de jugar al LoL tu vida es una
[ __ ] your parents hate you so study
[__] tus padres te odian pue estudiar
do something finish the [ __ ]
haz algo termina el [__] fp de
computer science FP that you started son of a [ __ ]
informática que empezaste hijo de [__]
get out of bed cockroach rat
levante de la cama cucaracha rata
insect Get up and do something with your life
insecto Levántate y haz algo con tu vida
already German Garcia carro better known
ya Germán García carro mejor conocido
as orlock was born on April 10, 1995
como orlock naci un 10 de Abril de 1995
in Betanzos, Spain. This young orlock
en betanzos España de Este joven orlock
inspired by American youtubers became
inspirado por youtubers americanos
interested in creating content
interesó por la creación de contenido
creating his main channel on September 19, 2012
creando un 19 de septiembre de 2012 su
under the name orlock
canal principal bajo el nombre de orlock
1080p for the following year to upload his
1080p para el año siguiente subir sus
first videos
primeros videos
diz Panther map Our goal is
diz mapa de Pantera Nuestro objetivo es
simple find an aerial vehicle and
sencillo encontrar un vehículo aéreo y
try to get out of this
tratar de salir vivos de esta
Island alive So let's get to it this was the
Isla Así que vamos a ello esto era la
original idea it wasn't even  mia was
idea original ni siquiera era mía estaba
trying to copy an
intentando copiarme de un canal
American channel that did this very well this
americano que hacía esto muy bien est
was a million 15 years old trying trying to
era millo de 15 años intentar intentando
copy this whatever is
copiar esto lo que esté
there Oh what a cringe what a cringe no no no pu
ahí Ay qué cringe qué cringe no no no pu
not defining his Style well varying his
no definiendo bien su Estilo variando Su
content between Gameplays and short
contenido entre Gameplays y cortos de
humor there are two things that you can not
humor hay dos cosas que no le puedes
do to him a banana offer him a banana and
hacer un plátano ofrecerle un plátano y
put on Death metal But why is he
ponerle Death metal Pero por qué me
yelling at me What's wrong Why is he
grita Qué pasa Por qué me
yelling at me guys I brought the snack
grita chicos traigo la merienda
for But why was he friends with Win michu
para Pero por qué era amigo de Win michu
os loock I mean what contact did they have
os loock O sea qué qué contacto tenían
if some were from Galicia
si unos de Galicia
and the other from
y el otro de
Madrid time to find their
Madrid el tiempo encontrar el suyo
own generating content that went
propio generando un contenido que iba
from criticism to analysis
desde las críticas hasta los análisis
several of these inspired again
varios de estos inspirándose nuevamente
by videos of American creators
en videos de creadores americanos
being able to say that these were copies
pudiéndose decir que estas eran copias
but nevertheless not entirely
pero sin embargo no siéndolo del todo ya
since the difference between the
que la diferencia que haba entre los
videos from which orlock got the
videos de los cuales orlock sacaba las
ideas differs a lot with the style of
ideas difiere mucho con el estilo de
this one when carrying them out generating as
este al llevarlas a cabo generando como
Magno Bravo said in his video about
lo dijo Magno Bravo en su video sobre
orlock a video that is not entirely a
orlock un video que no es del todo una
copy but the interpretation of
copia sino la interpretación de
orlock hear that Last Part but it
orlock hear that Last Part but it
sounded important destin For what not
sounded important destin For what not
only is that pretty funny but it allows
only is that pretty funny but it allows
Us to fill in the blank Our is mega Mind
Us to fill in the Blank Our is mega Mind
destined For greatness heroism
destined For greatness heroism
Destruction decay What well That's up
Destruction decay What well That's up
For him To I don't understand what they're
For him To no entiendo esto que me están
putting here what is it Guess
poniendo aquí qu es lo que es Guess
for n
for
two Start conflicting mind is raised
n two Start conflicting meind is raised
to think That burglar good police Bad
to think That burglar good police Bad
Ah so you're putting me an
Ah o sea me estás poniendo un vídeo
American video you're destined for and now the
gringo estás destinado para y ahora la
version of
versión de
orlock I didn't get today well the last
orlock no llegué a hoy bien la última
part but it seemed important destined
parte pero parecía importante destinado
for what megaman arrives on Earth and
para qué megaman llega a la Tierra y
lands directly in the jail where he
aterriza directamente en la cárcel donde
is educated by prisoners and his notion of
es educado por presos y su noción del
good and evil is based on things like the
bien y el mal se basa en cosas como la
police is not cool to steal It's the best there is
policía no Mola robar Es lo mejor que
eh mega is a bit in Plan G gun
hay eh mega es un poco en Plan G gun
[ __ ] gun
shit gun
[ __ ] interpretation which showed us
shit interpretación la cual nos mostraba
a completely new editing style
un estilo de edición completamente nuevo
for the platform style that to
para la plataforma estilo que a día de
this day we can still see in other creators
hoy aún podemos ver en otros creadores
which I'm sure were inspired by
los cuales estoy seguro se inspiraron en
orlog or someone who in turn was inspired
orlog o alguien que a su vez se inspiró
by this yes yes I liked the edition
en este sí sí la edición me gustaba a mí
eh it was
eh era
like the orlock style eh Solo  so you can
como es el estilo orlock eh Solo para
see how this works the same
que vean Cómo funciona esto la misma
section the success and the fall is inspired
sección el éxito y la caída se inspira
by three channels merluzo with its section
en tres canales merluzo con su sección
of water and the fall of video games dibra
del auga y la caída de videojuegos dibra
with its section of stories of
con su sección de historias de
bodybuilders and magnus mephisto with his
culturistas y magnus mefisto con su
channel the day that I talk about
canal el día que ya que yo hable de
stories of creators is a
historias de creadores es una decisión
purely marketing decision So it will be
meramente de marketing Entonces será
important for me to clarify this because I
importante para mí aclarar esto pues no
was not simply looking for how to
Simplemente estaba buscando Con qué
lengthen the video by returning to orlock his
alargar el video volviendo a orlock su
style when making these videos
Estilo a la hora de hacer estos videos
added to his participation in Col
sumado a su participación en Col
Salvador raya collaborations with other
Salvador raya colaboraciones con otros
great youtubers like El Rubius
youtubers Grandes como El Rubius
made this quickly increase
hicieron que rápidamente este aumentar
in popularity creating what in my
en popularidad creando lo que A mi
opinion is one of the strongest communities
parecer es una de las comunidades más
on the internet a community which would
fuertes de internet comunidad la cual
only show what it is capable of with
solo mostraría de lo que es capaz con la
orlog's foray into
incursión de orlog en
Twitch how are you how are my
Twitch qué tal qué tal mis jugadores
epic fortnite players how are you How long
épicos de fortnite qué tal Cuánto tiempo
how
cuánto
long how has your life been in this
tiempo cómo os ha ido la vida en este
How long has it been a month without
Cuánto ha sido un mes sin
live
directos madre
my mother if there are Peña subscribing Thank you
mía si hay Peña suscribiéndose Muchas
very much thank you now I'm going to do
gracias muchas gracias ahora voy a hacer
the usual role okay I'm going to go
la rola de siempre de acuerdo Voy a a
through why I say role  it's an expression
pasar por qué digo rola es una expresión
that I never use in my life and now
que nunca utilizo en mi vida y ahora
here live I go eh I'm going to put
aquí en directo me sale eh voy a poner
the intro that I like something that I
la intro que me gusta una cosa que
really enjoy doing and then eh
disfruto mucho hacer y ya pues eh
live normal whatever the
directo normal lo que [__]
[ __ ] but with this song Thank you it is so that
sea pero con esta canción Gracias es así
since 2018 both orsl and its
que desde 2018 tanto orsl como su
community would be an important part
comunidad formarían parte importante Ya
Not only in the history of YouTube but
no solo de la historia de YouTube sino
also in the
también de la historia de Twitch ya que
history of Twitch since the way its chat had to interact with it added to the closeness of orlock with them so much so that orlock was one of the first streamers to use redit so that his community could send him content to which he could react, these being mostly
reaccionar siendo estos en su mayoría
memes, made something like this, which at
memes hicieron que algo como esto que en
that time was unusual, to this day
ese tiempo era poco usual a día de hoy
is almost indispensable within the
sea casi indispensable dentro de la
dynamics of the streams and let's go that the
dinámica de los streams y vamos que la
influence of orlock in the way of
influencia de orlock en la forma de
managing the content created in Look, the
gestionar el contenido creado en Mira
cocu comes out here Stream does not stop here
sale el cocu aquí Stream no para aquí ya
since thanks to him the
que gracias a él se popularizaron los
secondary channels dedicated to summarizing
canales secundarios dedicados a resumir
the content made in Stream became popular, something
el contenido hecho en Stream algo
essential for youtubers who
indispensable para los youtubers que se
switch to live broadcasts or streamers who
pasen a los directos o los streamers que
want to gain more audience  as an example
quieran ganar más público como muestra
of this, this channel in a short time
de esto este canal en poco tiempo
doubled the number of subscribers of its
duplicó la cifra de suscriptores de su
main channel, I've told you before, I've
canal principal os lo he dicho antes os
told you before, a channel which he
lo he dicho antes canal el cual con el
eventually left to focus on his new
tiempo dejó para centrarse en su nueva
facet
faceta
as a streamer. Oh yes, the main channel
como streamer Ah sí el canal principal
no longer
ya no
exists, I mean, the main channel doesn't exist, it doesn't exist,
existe o sea el canal principal no
the
existe no existe el canal
main channel, how
principal qué
strong, how
fuerte qué
strong, it doesn't
fuerte no
exist, I didn't know
existe no sabía
that, lately there's been a lot of talk
eso últimamente se estado hablando mucho
about the Andorra issue, so even though I'm
del tema andorra así que a pesar de que
probably going to get into trouble, I
seguramente me vaya a meter en un lío
want to take this opportunity to give my
quiero aprovechar para dar mi
opinion
opinión
outside of the type of humor that Orlock
fuera del tipo de humor que orlock
handled and the passionate community
manejaba y la comunidad tan apasionada
that he had, it's very surprising that
que este tenía sorprende mucho que en
throughout his career he hasn't gotten into
toda su carrera no se haya metido en
many controversies, of course there was one, there was a
muchas polémicas claro hubo una hubo una
controversy,
polémica
eh, I don't remember what it was, I think it was a girl who accused him of flirting with her and being unfaithful to a girlfriend with her and the girl said she was underage but in reality she meant she was 18, 17 years old, I don't remember, he was banned from Twitch more than seven times, but he said
en más de siete ocasiones pero é soltaba
things like, "Alright, [ __ ]" and well, you know
cosas como al [__] y pues ya saben
how Twitch gets with  regarding
cómo se pone Twitch con respecto a
some matters But among the few that we
algunos asuntos Pero entre las pocas que
can mention is the time he was
podemos mencionar esta la vez que le fue
unfaithful to his girlfriend at the time Abi
infiel a su novia de ese entonces Abi
with an 18 year old girl some of you have
con una chica de 18 años algunos habéis
found out exactly what I'm
enterado justo lo que estoy
saying others haven't This happened like in the
diciendo otros no Esto ocurrió como por
summer of last year so
verano el año pasado así la está siendo
a girl is being with me with another girl and when this
una chica me l con otra y cuando esta
information arrived t is L vast and
información lleg t se L vastísimo y lo
what and because it has or rather because it is
que y por tiene o sea porque está
explaining this controversy with him what was this
explicando esta polémica con el cómo se
name this was the one who won the
llamaba este este fue el que le Gan el
trial this
juicio este
year that threatened me do you remember Why did he
año que me amenazó os acordáis Por qué
threaten me because I put a meme no or something
me amenazó porque puse un meme no o algo
like that not from the masi which is like well let's
así no de la masi que es como bueno a
see gave and sent me like Well he threatened me
ver dio y me mandó como Bueno me amenazó
publicly and then he
públicamente y luego
threatened me publicly and then he
me me amenazó públicamente y luego me
sent me privately also the threats
mandó por privado también las amenazas
of the stick that you know that I have warned you eh
del palo que sepas que te He avisado eh
you had I don't remember what he said to me
te había no me acuerdo que me dijo
exactly but it was something like I don't know very very
exactamente pero era algo como no sé muy
heavy very heavy that like the [ __ ] what did I
muy heavy muy heavy que como [__] qué es
do I knew it was because of that like the
lo que he hecho sabía era por lo de que
[ __ ] this what the [ __ ]
como [__] esto qué [__]
is How many viewers did Oslo have I don't
es Cuántos espectadores tenía oslo No lo
know they sentenced him  eh they convicted him I
sé lo condenaron eh lo condenaron le
won the trial they convicted him
gané el juicio lo condenaron
and I don't know if he already paid and all that I think
y no sé si ya pagó y todo eso creo
also but I don't know why he has it on
además pero no sé por qué lo tiene en
screen Ah because I put masi against
pantalla Ah porque puse masi contra
murán it's true it's true and then It
murán es verdad es verdad y luego
turns out that IB himself offered them
Resulta ser que el propio IB les ofreció
a
un combate de
boxing match it happened and he lost the appeal too
boxo ocurrió y perdió el recurso también
Román passed Of having cheated on
Román pasó De haberle puesto los cuernos
my girlfriend which is all
a mi novia lo cual es todo términos
relative terms because Well I'm not going to
relativos porque Bueno ya no voy a
discuss with anyone how my
discutir con nadie cómo estaba mi
relationship was what the terms of my
relación cuá son los términos de mi
relationship are What things had happened things had
relación Qué cosas habían pasado cosas
n't happened in my relationship I don't
no habían pasado en en mi relación no
have with anyone that I don't love at least
tengo con nadie que yo no quiera menos
on Twitter but with this information l
por Twitter pero cu esta información l
I paid the trial Juan Well I don't know
el juicio lo pagó yo Juan Pues no lo sé
I imagine Because he went with a lawyer he
me imagino Porque él fue con abogado él
went with a lawyer and and lawyers are not
fue con abogado y y los abogados no son
cheap lawyers are not cheap but it is
baratos los abogados no son baratos pero
true that he asked to
sí que es verdad que él pidió como
split the payment they put him like I do
fraccionar el pago le pusieron como un
n't know from what my lawyer told me eh I do
no sé por lo que me dijo mi abogado eh
n't know if I'm explaining it well but
No sé si lo estoy explicando bien pero
like he had a time to pay and he
como que tenía un tiempo para pagar y Él
asked to split it I think it was or something like that I do
pidió fraccionarlo creo que fue o algo
n't remember but of course
así no me acuerdo pero claro eso
evidently probably the lawyer I
evidentemente seguramente el abogado O
mean if not  has money to pay I don't know
sea si no tiene dinero para pagar No sé
if he was sentenced to 600 700 or something like that or
si le condenaron a 600 700 o algo así o
and Costa I don't remember okay
y Costa no me acuerdo vale
and if you don't have to pay 600 euros how did you
e si no tienes para pagar 600 eur cómo
allow yourself a lawyer So I
te has permi un abogado Entonces yo me
imagine that and I Juan would say well
imagino que eso y yo Juan diría bueno
okay You know but I apologized in public
vale Sabes pero pedí perdón en público
that little bit apologize in public or
eso poquito pedir perdón en público o
say something my friend has done this for me
decir algo mi amigo ha hecho esto por mí
or whatever you know No no that that nothing that
o lo que sea sabes No no eso eso nada
nothing Neither before nor after the trial we
eso nada Ni antes ni después del juicio
are going to try to keep quiet the
vamos a intentar callarnos que cuanta
less people know the better and outside tter yes it
menos gente lo sepa mejor y fuera tter
all went crazy because I don't have
se se se volvió loquísimo todo por no
the ball man the thing
tengo el cherino puesto tío la cuestión
is that to this day man I have to I have to
es que al día de hoy tío tengo que tengo
read comments eh talking about my
que leer comentarios eh hablando de mi
life as if they were finally uploading something man
vida como si almente subieran algo tío
calling me That if stalker on the one hand
llamándome Que si acosador por un lado
that if I have been with minors [ __ ]
que si he estado con con menores [__]
[ __ ] man what is clear is that what
gilipolleces tío lo que está claro es
is clear is that a fact that
que lo que está claro que un hechos que
never in my life I have been with anyone
nunca en mi vida he estado con nadie
underage the girl with whom I
menor de edad la chica con la que le
cheated on my girlfriend had way I
puse los cuernos a mi novia tenía modo
cheated on my girlfriend had  18
le puse los cuernos a mi novia tenía 18
years old This is how it is this is a fact eh
años Esto es así esto es un hecho eh
but you know how Twitter works and it
pero ya sabes cómo funciona Twitter y me
really pisses me off it really pisses me off
toca mucho la peña me toca mucho la
man Because in the end people on
[__] tío Porque la peña al final en
Twitter are like they get on a [ __ ]
Twitter es como se suben una [__] tío
moral high ground man of being [ __ ] anonymous and they
esca moral tío de ser [__] anónimos y
judge the lives of other people with a [ __ ]
juzgan la vida de otra Peña con una [__]
moral superiority man and Maria it's funny
superioridad moral tío y María gracia
seeing all these Twitter people man with
ver toda esta Peña de Twitter tío con
[ __ ] years and soccer [ __ ] Maria
[__] añ y putasas de fútbol María
Thank you very much getting into their [ __ ] life
Muchas gracias entrar en su [__] vida
man and seeing what the [ __ ] they've done in their lives
tío y ver qué [__] han hecho en su vida
man to allow themselves to comment on
tío para permitirse comentar las [__]
people's [ __ ] [ __ ] as if they
movidas de la gente como si ellos lo
did everything right in their [ __ ] life man And the thing is that
hiciesen todo bien en su [__] vida tío Y
the relationship between Abi and orlock in
es que la relación entre Abi y orlock de
the public eye seemed conflictive it's
cara al público parecía conflictiva es
true eh man Abi was de's girlfriend
verdad eh tío Abi era la novia de de
Well in fact I think that her rise to
Bueno de hecho creo que su salto a la
fame is that no since there were multiple
fama es ese no ya que eran múltiples las
occasions in which both of them ended their
ocasiones en que ambos terminaban su
relationship to then get back
relación para luego volver a estar
together dynamic that broke with his
juntos dinámica que se rompió con la
infidelity towards Abi oslog
infidelidad de este hacia Abi oslog
being attacked by people who called him
siendo atacado por gente que lo tachaba
filo this despite the fact that the other
de filo esto a pesar de que la otra
girl was
chica tenía
18 But well basically that what
18 Pero bueno básicamente eso que que
I have trusted For a year and a
que yo he confiado Durante un año y
half I have allowed a thousand things I have let them
medio he permitido mil cosas he dejado
treat me in a thousand ways Ah I
que se me tratara de Mil maneras Ah yo
started when I was 19 years old I lived at
empecé cuando tenía 19 años yo vivía
my parents' house I was very small and
casa de mis padres era muy pequeñita y
of course a person much older than
claro te viene una persona muy mayor que
you comes along bu quite older than you and well they can
tú bu bastante mayor que tú y pues puede
do whatever they want to you and that's what they
hacer contigo lo que quiera y eso que
did
hizo
Ah what happens is that there are a lot of people who
Ah qué pasa que hay mucha gente que
will think buah these people leave him or come back or
pensará buah estos lo deja ni vuelve ni
leave him or it's worth it I always said that the
lo deja ni vale Yo siempre dije que en
moment I found out that there
el momento en el que me enterará de que
were 1 people Ah I was going to
habían 1 personas Ah yo me iba a
completely disengage Ah I
desentender completamente Ah Esto me lo
promised myself this because as much as I
prometí a mí misma porque por mucho que
let them trample on me in certain ways there are no
dejé que me pisotear en ciertas maneras
others in which I don't want them to trample on me
no hay otras en las que no quiero que me
and of course I was always looking the
y claro yo siempre estuve mirando hacia
other way on this subject many people
otro lado en este tema mucha gente me
wrote to me I found many messages and even
escribió encontré muchos mensajes y aún
so I didn't want to accept it but well the
así no lo quise aceptar pero pues ha
time has come that it's over Hi you see in
llegado momento que ya está Hola ves en
wh Darío well man This was brutal eh the
qu Darío pues tío Esto fue brutal eh lo
punch was brutal eh
del puñetazo fue brutal
whatever Look at the punch that I threw at him
eh sea Mira el puñetazo que le he metido
man I mean the  punch was brutal eh there
tío o sea lo del puñetazo fue brutal eh
came a time that it's done Hello in that it is
lleg momento que ya está Hola en qu sea
trust what he did to him and the other did like this
fíate lo que le hizo y el otro hizo así
reflex action pum
acto reflejo pum
well and How does it sound also
pues y Cómo suena además
eh You are a son of a [ __ ] what happened
eh Eres un hijo de [__] qué ha pasado
that he broke a tooth [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
que me ha roto un diente cabrón hostias
[ __ ] And it's that Darío who is part of the
hostias Y es que Darío qui forma parte
podcast and the
del podcast y
internet you the other one just joking and the
internet tú el otro así de broma y el
other one reacts like I mean that's a that's a that's
otro Reacciona como o sea eso es
a reaction that is
una eso es una eso es una reacción que
surely because he's used
seguramente es porque está acostumbrado
to fighting and things
a pelearse y cosas
like that And it's that
así Y es
punch like that that breaks
que puñetazo de esa manera que le rompe
a tooth and it's a friend, so you
un diente a y es un amigo o sea que tú
're in an environment like how are you going to
estás en un ambiente sea cómo vas a
react Like this Pay attention to how you're going to
reaccionar Así Fíjate cómo vas a
react like how you react on the
reaccionar así cómo reaccionas en la
street then I mean if knowing that you
calle entonces O sea si sabiendo que
are on a live program and the
estás en un programa en directo y los
two next to you are your friends, you
dos que tienes al lado son tus amigos te
recently reacted by breaking his mouth,
hace poco reaccionar partiéndole la boca
me who is part of the podcast and the
yo quien forma parte del podcast y
internet together with orlock would have a
interneto junto a orlock tendría una
very disproportionate reaction to a
reacción muy desproporcionada ante un
game of this action that in 2021 was
jugueteo de este acción que en 2021 fue
one of the most viral clips on the internet
uno de los clips más virales de internet
with several creators  reacting to this
con varios creadores reaccionando a esto
what caused Dari off camera
lo que ocasionó que darí fuera de cámara
is visibly affected by
se encuentra visiblemente afectado por
what happened affected because he did it
lo que pasó afectado porque lo ha hecho
in public and because they caught him and
en público y porque le han pillado y
everyone is talking about
está todo el mundo hablando de
it like I'm going to blow up a tent but
eso en plan reviento un tiente pero
then I'm all scratched I'm a monster
después Estoy todo rayado soy un monstro
my life Do you think that with that face
mi vida Tú te crees que con esa cara
someone is going to think that you are that you are
alguien se va a pensar que eres que eres
evil with that face I am a
malito con esa cara soy un
monster Explain to me the historic moment
monst Me explicas el momento histórico
that I have had to live please eh I am
que me ha tocado vivir por favor eh soy
a And it is that during that time people and
un Y es que durante ese tiempo gente y
other creators harshly criticized him
otros creadores lo criticaban duramente
for what happened
por lo sucedido llegando a atacar
even attacking his wife for her sometimes
incluso a su mujer por sus en ocasiones
inappropriate feminist comments
desatinados comentarios feministas sin
however orsl who was the most
embargo orsl quien era el principal
affected by all this took the
afectado por todo esto se tomó la
situation from the beginning with humor
situación desde el principio con humor
talking to Dar and solving both
hablando con dar y solucionando ambas
things both behind and in front of
las cosas tanto detrás como delante de
the cameras I don't want to
las cámaras no quiero
do it deep down I don't want to do it dude it
hacerlo el fondo no quiero hacerlo tío
seems stupid to me really I mean
me parece estúpido de verdad O sea a
where does revenge lead dude what is this I
dónde lleva la venganza tío qué es esto
mean it really seems to me that here we
O sea de verdad me parece que hay
continue like the cycle of violence I mean I
seguimos como el ciclo de violencia o
think someone
sea creo que alguien
should and now for the
debería y ahora por el
spectacle be the arrangement spectacle
espectáculo sea el arreglo espectáculo
Is that he returns the host or  I think
Es que le devuelva la [__] o sea creo
someone
que alguien
should always say that I'm happy
debería cada vez esto que soy feliz
because I'm very happy with my life
porque estoy muy contento con mi vida
but I'm 25 years old and every day I feel
pero tengo 25 años y cada día me noto
more bitter than the last and it's
más amargado que el anterior y es una
something that's starting to worry me
cosa que me está empezando a preocupar
the psychologist who is not a good sign You're
el psicólogo que no es una buena señal
not going because we're already off to a bad start
No estás yendo pues ya mal empezamos
You know, I mean, I've been going for three months or
Sabes quiero decir yo levo tres meses o
so and if I wasn't going I
así yendo y si no estuviese yendo
'd be on rep and such I get up in
estaría de rep y tal yo me levanto por
the morning I pick up my phone in bed I open
la mañana cojo el móvil en la cama abro
Twitter and no I mean no no no because he's
Twitter y no O sea no no no porque me
talking to me but he starts reading
está hablando a mí pero empieza a leer
one one talking about his life that I don't give a
uno uno conando su vida que me suda la
[ __ ] another talking about ayus another I don't
[__] otro hablando de de ayus otro no
know what as a guy I don't need this in 2021
sé qué como tío no necesito esto en 2021
from one day to the next orlock simply
de un día para otro orlock simplemente
left many say that this was caused
se fue muchos dicen que esto fue causado
by the sum
por la suma
of personal problems that
de problemas personales que se le
orlock would have had at that
habrían presentado a orlock en ese
time among them we have the breakup
tiempo entre ellos tenemos la ruptura
with his girlfriend and the loss of a friend
con su novia y la pérdida de un amigo
others also say that he left because
otros también dicen que se fue porque no
he didn't like the limitations when
le gustó las limitaciones a la hora de
expressing himself that now he had Twitch but
expresarse que ahora Tenía Twitch pero
feeling so certain we will never know
siencia así cierta nunca sabremos el Por
exactly why  orlock made this
qué con exactitud orlock tomó esta
decision but what we do know is that it
decisión pero lo que sí sabemos es que
was the best thing for him because now I want to
fue lo mejor para él porque ahora quiero
make music and I mean it's not because of time it's not
hacer música y O sea no es por el tiempo
because of physical time it's not because it
no es por el tiempo físico no es porque
stole physical time because then he
me robe tiempo físico porque luego me
threw me at home What happened to him man he will
tió en casa Qué habrá sido de él tío
say something now here in the video hours
dirá algo ahora aquí en el vídeo horas
a day smoking for playing video games
al día fumando por jugando videojuegos
but I want to have the mental energy in
pero quiero tener la energía mental en
one place that's what I'm telling you I can't
un sitio es lo que te digo no puedo
live mental energy is totally
vivir energía mental es totalmente
intensive intensive take it away when I
intensible intensible quital cuando
have a more squared part then it
tenga una parte más cuadriculada pues
can allow you to talk with the other but
pueda permitir ttear con la otra pero
now for me they are you also have on a
ahora para mí son unas tienes también a
creative level you know if I have to be
nivel creativo sabes si tengo que estar
thinking about doing [ __ ] live
pensando en hacer [__] en directo
no no no s today orlock
no no no s a día de hoy orlock dejó por
completely left everything related to the
completo todo lo relacionado con la
creation of content to dedicate himself to
creación de contenido para dedicarse a
music 100% space in which he
la música al 100% espacio en el que él
says he feels better not showing to
dice sentirse mejor no mostrando hasta
this day intentions of returning to
el día de hoy intenciones de volver a
Twitch or YouTube and it doesn't seem like he's
Twitch o a YouTube y tampoco parece que
going to do it either since no I mean now he's
lo vaya hacer ya que no O sea ahora está
making music no no it has disappeared
haciendo música no no está desaparecido
at all a long time ago his YouTube channel
del todo hace mucho su canal de YouTube
was supposedly hacked He is managing to
fue supuestamente hackeado Este logrando
recover it but it can no longer be seen
recuperarlo pero ya no pudiéndose ver
None of the videos that this had Hey do
Ninguno de los videos que este tenía Oye
you miss anything everyone
echas de menos algo todo el mundo
streaming podcast something or are you
streaming podcast algo o estás
You've already cleared your mind completely and I do
Ya te has limpiado la mente del todo y
n't want to say it anymore because if I say it it
ya no lo quiero decir porque si lo digo
's like I'm signing a contract
es como que estoy firmando un contrato
but like yeah yeah for example There are days
pero en plan si si por ejemplo Hay días
when I legitimately feel like
que me apetece legítimamente hacer
streaming but to do the thing I
streaming pero por hacer rollo de me
feel like playing a game and commenting on it with
apetece jugar un juego y comentarlo con
people or talking about something talking about movies
la peña o hablar de algo hablar de pelis
with people or something You know I feel like
con la peña o algo Sabes Me apatece como
streaming like crazy but I know that
el rato echar streaming pero sé que
doing it is like signing a [ __ ] contract
hacerlo es como firmar un [__] contrato
that I'm going to screw up my life for another
del que me voy a [__] la vida otra
season in my personal opinion orlog
temporada a mi opinión personal orlog
did something that few
hizo algo que pocos creadores de
content creators dare to do today and that
contenido se animan hacer hoy en día y
is to stop doing something that does not fulfill them
es dejar de hacer algo que no les llena
and also begins to affect their
y además empieza a afectar su salud
mental health to move on to a project that they do
mental para pasar a un proyecto que sí
want to do but that
tengan ganas de hacer pero que
mainly makes them happy that is why
principalmente los haga felices es por
today We have so many
eso que a día de hoy Tenemos tantos
successes and falls because of people who do not know
éxitos y caídas por gente que no sabe
when to put an end to something that is
cuándo ponerle punto final a algo que
clearly doing them wrong
claramente les está haciendo mal
putting money before their
anteponiendo el dinero ante su salud
mental health and believe me that every single one of the
mental y créanme que cada uno de los
streamers that we see today  nowadays it's a
streamers que vemos hoy en día es una
time bomb about to explode but
bomba de tiempo a punto de explotar pero
of course there's also the case of those who
claro también está el caso de los que no
have no other option since neither we nor
tienen otra opción Ya que ni nosotros ni
they see themselves doing anything
ellos mismos se ven haciendo algo
different dehumanizing themselves
diferente deshumanizando a ellos mismos
and becoming a toy
y volviéndose en un juguete usado
constantly used humiliated and made by and
constantemente humillado y hecho por y
only for our entertainment and
solo para nuestro entretenimiento y
then Well I don't know if this is really like that
después Pues no lo sé si esto realmente
eh in the end I don't think all cases
eh al final no creo que todos los casos
are the same and that everyone has to
sean iguales y que todo el mundo tenga
have a beginning and an end on the
que tener un principio y un final en la
platform be it Twitch or YouTube or
plataforma ya sea Twitch o sea YouTube o
a television presenter a
sea un presentador de televisión un
television collaborator is
colaborador de televisión está toda la
on TV their whole life and that's it okay eh one thing
vida en la tele y punto vale eh una cosa
is that you take vacations that there are
es que te tomes vacaciones que haya
times when things are better for you and others
épocas en las que te vaya mejor y otras
worse And such But stop working You don't
peor Y tal Pero dejar de trabajar No
have to I mean why are you going to stop
tienes por qué O sea por qué vas a dejar
working unless you find something else
de trabajar a no ser que encuentres otra
that you like more and suits you better no
cosa que te guste más y te vaya mejor no
because I understand that if orlock
porque entiendo que si orlock
lived off that of
vivía de
course he earned a salary in the
eso del claro lo cobraba un sueldo en el
podcast another what he earned on his
podcast otro lo que cobraba él en su
Stream And such But of course if you quit What do you do you
Stream Y tal Pero claro si lo dejas Qué
have to make a living and
haces de algo tienes que vivir y la
music gives him a living I don't know okay
música le da para vivir No lo sé vale